Guide to the Breckenridge-Bates family papers, 1861-1902.
Breckenridge-Bates family papers, 1861-1902
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Breckenridge-Bates family papers, 1861-1902.
3352
Fred Bates, Juanita Breckenridge.
1.2 cubic ft.
Correspondence, financial records, business records, accounts, photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, financial records, business records, accounts, photographs, and other items deriving from the families of Fred E. Bates and Juanita Breckenridge of Ithaca, New York.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, financial records, business records, accounts, photographs, and other items deriving from the families of Fred E. Bates and Juanita Breckenridge of Ithaca, New York.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Breckenridge-Bates family.
Subjects:
Family--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Fred E. Bates and Family Papers
  - Papers, 1861-1872 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Papers, 1873-1874 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Papers, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Papers, 1876 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Papers, 1877 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Papers, 18882-1884; 1891 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - G.A.R. David Ireland Post #158 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Horse Hay-Rake, 1875; 1884 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Accounts, 1877; 1878,; n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Juanita Breckenridge Papers
  - Correspondence, 1872-1880 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1881-1883 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1884 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1887-June 1887 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, July 1887-Dec. 1887 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 188-July 1888 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 1888-Dec. 1888 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1889 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1891 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1892-Aug. 1892 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 1892-Dec. 1892 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1894-1902 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Breckenridge-Bates Family Papers
  - Miscellaneous and Memorabilia, 1876; 1882,; 1885-1888,; 1892,; 1893 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Viola Enterprise, March 16, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Financial Documents, 1872-1894 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Insurance Policies, 1874-1897 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Packages (4) Drafts, c. 1872-1897 (Box 3)
  - Volumes Checkbooks, c. 1872-1897 (Box 3)